Or are.
Poor. One
day when. You're
a boy. Or
a war or.
When.
Your with
a war. When. You're
. Poor.
Brett brought the
prayer or
put her. My Royal they can be
a rock on. Me colder than
a basement wall the only moment I keep
waiting for is when the day will be brought
. Home I never know the doc or
clear hock able to say to me I
hardly hear
a passing hours are and I'm glad you're
here until at last I'm all where.
Every night at seven. You log
in as fresh as all around
I began to sigh all over again I'm
a. Harebrained I.
Come by like they are returning and
me by I thought in your owning
a. Car You seem to bring. Are Always great
need me. I always am bored.
When you're in
a room Red Rain. But.
Every time the same thing
happened I bought one again and
then love Bob only with your.
Air.
I.
Mean I say your performance was
a bit ragged so slow going problem
with Scotch but I think I.
Recall. You would. Still have probably
turned it off and save money. To.
Leave the house if you want to know that
one thing is the end of the past year and
a half
a week. But you're right so I can see. To
him to keep his air condition can't take
it with him when he's going in maybe
flying cars if ever I play King again I'm
going to be one of those Asiatic boys who
just waits givings in the cheap. What's
your hurry paid how Alan what I find you
waiting you have the don't know I don't
believe in bed. I'm fine thank you friend
I'm not fond of my speaking the phone I
make use of one just as on
anyone. Oh I wasn't so hot
oh I'm your knees in style guides you so
I think what brought him up is clammy
night. Just told me to tell you it was
impose if you're in the center need to make
up a spot on the floor in all forms
Oh Ellen. Irving wants us to meet him
a gothic OK how do you like me if we
can't use the sound no what Ellen honey
nails or what against your own
mouth must the back nine of
a gin and tonic your intent and then two
days ago I know this one thousand and
fifty mad about it not all I thought I. Was
and seems like they can don't see this
will probably be one of those long
affairs that right going to hold me to
a conversation turns
a while wedding and let them read its
capital is already best and I'm happy and
anticipation of the wedding which is still
several weeks out and the press is the
most partly got it secret
in England since radar is
a way to go. First time this week
it. Chester out of Miami Florida
a new tropical hurricane things to be
approaching and I'm talking on yes you know
it's the moment that's developed the square
of the day her grandfather was married
I give everything to be there again the
spoken Jew as I like weddings provided of
course they're not mine although
it is a very healthy isn't just
a married man they're much longer than
bachelor that's true they're only trying to
outlive their wives so they can
be bachelors again and you have
a daughter getting there it's
a matter of fact I did it and they changed
their mind at the last moment I've been
deeply indebted to have
a sense of connection. There with
the lettering on some of. The
clues like so many boys that
when all of the Bank of Japan
a strong the thing money
does. Not it wasn't bad.
In that I didn't I'm going to be denied.
The only thing he's done and I know.
I have
a good life what is with the deal with
this is I was the show that with. The
I looked the sleep tonight. OK
come on or I have no I haven't.
Accomplished a great. Bed
is the square of. Me with
a rod tell you. My brother Reg
calls and I thank them. And
they said that if people want to hold KNOW
WHAT THEY WANT TO THE during the wedding
season they learned during
the way it's not like that.
But soon as possible because she got her
things Katherine. What about presentation
. Which one of the main was
the French. Janet Yellen this
means would be sanctified and ten day
nine No we're happy. I was when we
back. To the critics like
and with the result of.
What are you doing with me what am I doing
here for what are you doing I don't tell
you baby that's an insult what's in it
so what's the matter with you you're not
going to get what has. All of that. Kind
of thing with me I think. I have to I
haven't heard. Any of us and the rest of
the company of the week I feel if I want
to I don't know them and when you're sure
how much that we. Can't keep the change.
Coming. I have
a little business on. And off the list
by the Pentagon. Thank.
You. And don't know if the
laughing stock of. Your home let's go
right now walking up the gangplank that
you like. Best about.
I was
a good pilot. I miss you very much and I
can tell you that knowing that these past
few weeks in the name of the most
exciting thing that happened.
I thought I was the wrong day we had
regular and I had so much to say oh well
you're going to be away I'm not and suddenly
knowing you're going to be away makes
me realize my feelings for you so I
thought I'd. Eleanor. Saw that and if
you're going to. Pay my way I can
tell you about the knowing these
past few weeks of the most
exciting thing that I have to.
Abide by I know you'll be
a smash you want anything else my brother
Edgar is going to meet at the hotel by.
The pearl and I.
Know I'm. Right that arrived.
At by. I'm going to get on the.
Plane. Thank goodness.
The
pattern and the AI.
On
a beautiful day will go back to that one
the song about we can have fun together I
just yeah I prefer the day. The God.
I don't I want a Bible that
is OK but don't forget we got
a rehearsal because I'm two o'clock sharp
jam I won't keep you long I'll be like
a. Good
day to this kind of in the
middle of working on. Not
writing a letter I'm just doing waiting
for the opportunity. My name is Brenda
a lot younger than what you
believe that is about I
really was seen as
a big piece that I wish.
Boeing was close your
eyes and go and not you you're doing fine
they stripped it of me I should know when
I saw your show a few weeks ago this
week well that's all right and I have
a lot on your mind. I can explain those
two little episodes to within just like
a camp yes then go ahead Oh. Well
you see they're both terribly
nice girls and they're both so fond of me
that I and I can bet Bing one up you know
how it is in order to be
kind of people one has to be
a very very good liar to tell me why are
you following me when I knew what I was
doing no such thing I
was only saying if I do
a couple of the same. This
is sort of thing I have
New York where all the time and you come
I get there but you kind of have to
and. You never really are and no I've been
on business some time but I'm just going
on the way the runaway yes you're going
to the wedding but I miss going home I
guess when the reading of the light I
just I'm afraid so. Haven't you ever met
anyone who held
a title of your own your little. You know
I'm very glad Joyland know it now because
it means that chap you with
a job by them at your house you know what
I didn't know what I saw they this whole
boat and I discovered that you were the
most attractive girl on girl thank you and
I kept thinking what
a pity she's mad because that's going to
make things terrible. But it isn't going
to be over the top now thanks for the use
of our present not the thought of you see
my fist drawn back with her I'm waiting
for please we are I like you about I'm
going to miss you so much a boy and I have
a favor to up on Haven't causing you
know we have a got a benefit but there's
a Bill C.
Men and I was wondering if you and your
sister would dance but us on that night
we'd love to just tell us when just one
long that would be sufficient we don't want
to have to do it all trouble it's all I
know it's an imposition to ask you to but I
would just let love to
don't worry we'll do it.
And of all don't take yes for an answer.
Oh.
Wow.
I am honey.
I'm all right
thanks.
Thanks thanks.
Thanks thanks thanks.
I'm. Right.
Let.
Let let. Let.
Let let let let
let let let
let let let.
Let let let.
Let us. See he
he. Thinks
. Oh by thank the showing up for hurdles
are also John this is my brother Tom Tom
Just how do you know that I'm right I think
I'm John writing room so I gather the
real tough thing to me I don't cate.
How to study very separate
which is. Let's get people to
show it because.
The hour. Panicked and then after that
yeah the poster boy I'm wondering if you
and your sister would best right away
instead of with the walk down puppy little
a bit of the weather you know but be
a little rocky Yes that will bother to think
about let the banks every time you say
.
All right.
Mother on. The palm of.
Her the hour are.
The in. The. Media.
All girl. With
me the.
The. Way it.
All. All
or. All we want.
Is. Holding
a. Room.
On the whole. All day is.
World. War
all. Of the world.
Or all world. All
right
a. Warmer earlier
or all the or.
The whole. World War
World War I World War World
War war war war or.
All right all
right I
can handle the I mean you're
around all your. Move.
The. Move not sorry but what Martin.
Or wall.
Or
a the or. During
. All right.
Or wrong. But I.
Didn't want to store it.
And I'll. Yes Oh sure yes you have to come
on up run to eleven twelve and fourteen
OK Was that
a good cleaner I think it's coming
up. I still have her me and what
the print doing this morning was a
caller and asking I know what I'm doing
a month before I was
probably trying to figure
a way to get out of it you need to think
so you know you would know what I.
Hope to do I'm
a good thing it oh. We didn't know that
I'm going to I would win no we didn't why
my favorite you should have told
you you know after all this is
a pretty box of pickles May I come in
because I'm sorry how do you think this is
all happening to me to at long last my
it's amazing as it is other than that I do
hope the rules are satisfactory then all
that fine miracle you get them so yes
quite the wedding has backed things up
a bit but then there are lives happening
that it all seems to be humming the dance
of the coming to audition
with optimising is tomorrow.
Well the Chinese are in it and the romantic
John Brennan Dale you know I know the
family very little that they do say
that young gentleman is a bit of
a chaser in that case very hard after
Ellen she stood still and waited this
afternoon another auditioning audience just
next time you know to me this afternoon
doing how much meta data honesty is all
country homes I suppose it's all right but
I think you want to come along and see
who you're working with I never notice
anyone but you just I want you home for
dinner and no dates at night until after we
open you come struggling in at four o'clock
in the morning the all tied up next day
yes. I thought that the time you
pick me at OK having an item.
Showing up for yourself and be back all
how we're just playing games Oh and if
there's anything you need to call thank
you after you. Tell me oh boy how things
are the colonies these days go on I want.
These English clothes reading
frankly amusing time what Yeah. I.
Got
a match. Back I hear
that shaving lotion. Oh
everything. Sorry I thought
you were him on the.
Back of the OP if you know what the better
is don't allow people like that yellow.
Or red. Blue out.
Of the. Hello again I wish you'd stop
bothering. I'm not
a bit. Loose.
The poor.
Around I'm child got your statement
everything's ready. To get on the green grass
near the end changing issues
yes. They can each step break.
You know name an ash. You
begin to forget this an ash.
The the.
Rocky steps of me please. See that
as a partner and I couldn't in
a moment ago which would take something
easy to start mapping up least
the all.
Should have seen expression on the basis
on how did I know if I'm right then.
That's very well thank you I think
you'll do the phone when I get the song.
And I think what I know
of what happened and I do
a little bit more looking I did not do it
with me so when I had left about tonight
when I don't know I had to buy it with
a thank you. So
much for that hour almost that. I had
to put it. You know what if the down
at the wedding present we held back
having at auction someone said
a couple of China but. I was about to get
those I got the thing especially the
chance that we decide to have them out
of the principle that what the president
said Oh I don't know I think you have to
enjoy living ourself Well you know to ask
anyone else to judge and. Here we are.
Told. A. God
you know.
I think that yeah. Oh I
want to go. Along with
you all about. I want to but I'd
like to. I met you miss it terribly
No I don't think I do anymore I just don't
have any replies. I think what I'm going
to be back seven times I wish that I didn't
I don't know when I get out of reading
there's some thought about it every
night. CONTRA. I don't have time
when you try to get down to good.
Back on top of the afternoon Oh well
how you then that when you do that.
I've got
a Tod I thought I'd just skip dinner and
go straight to bed your mind oh no no it's
a good idea that you're really not. Sure
you know much oh gosh now I got it right
now you write. In
a kind of rough day. About
how you can act. The
the. The
the. The the.
The the.
The past.
The I've. Heard
the
black.
Tank. Shells. Like the. Hard
work. What made you decide. To sell
well when I was eleven I
did not backpack with
a boy much. Well. His name with
a long time and I was aware that suddenly
when I want that. So I figured if I dance
and I was happy I should be happy.
That's any other. I think so. I felt so
good about anon I used to close my eyes
because I could dance all over the wall
even the ceiling if you
haven't learned to do that to
a very good book. You
better not take. Why not and it's
a long winded side this is Friday Friday I
have to stop to see my father or like me
the camera What's the address hundred fifty
meters coverage six want this image of
free love the government must do.
What it misses Dr Oz love for government
the that's why bother with the press all
day I do really want to send you the quite
impossible rant here my mother been
separated for three years and I have to
stop at every Friday guess I'm wondering
what we're doing and I'm speaking to John
so I see him and brought it me time to
get boarding on the back
but you know you become
a blooming use and much more
every time you fall down get to
a piece out of the bar with your chin so
I think somehow on an NG Well it will go
our duty and done it my father thought of
it is tons of that name is actually used
to make it that there's a royal not felony
I use an overly Bone who told me that
a girl we used to know named their glasses
Oxy I don't think that is any funny up
in the way of you then when I go really
who are right out of the window nobody
knows why but I won't be getting much of
an anonymous I don't suppose you'll be any
later Why no I don't believe I have any
relatives over here you see I'm from
America America I'm going to get out
of my company the president I'm not on
speaking of the United States out there
you're bringing another Yank to my cabin
here out on
a second what's the matter with your arms
that you will not get can really. Look at
these two pounds and run up your bloomin
soldiers and one of the DO WHAT ABOUT HIM
I'm not stopping as
a royal not. Well no I can't allow
Anglo-American relations read like this I'd like
to swear that Bill Dugan should show
how much is that to pass him. Now that
a gentleman not a toll like that of
a young actress Oh yes well now you can
just add ten bob to that and give it to me
to mother and she found out when you go to
the post you are if you keep it from me
repugnant Jane she was sent to prison
talking to the wrong Hinds As for the bank
the court and the papers anybody who did
are allowed to see the wedding presents
a nice custom three pas
to me Oh all right here
what you come for don't
you trust me that's like
a mother like your five sling
shot that's what you might call
a typographical error. Thank you we
better go and I cannot bear it when I
tell my buddy there's
a royal cap. Thanks
looks like mother to this and she Jamie
separate You can never get to sleep like
that Walkman at my special part by.
The yank your thumb on our right it might
help. You don't sound very happy that
I am going to grip no. But it is
ridiculous he's in Chicago Illinois you
know and you live here and when you get
that arrangement after your marriage to be
very happy. Along which
it seems like two years.
When I'm up with and I've never
thought of not being. You're from
a very off every few days. Or
actually I have two months but
you'd probably be. Arrested I think Tony
and I was in your show and asked him to
call the opening night. I assume you have
planned on getting together. You going
over there the coming over here in the
middle middle. You see he works in over his
department store in Chicago while listen
if he makes enough that your I make enough
to do with and the man that's on. You
you don't. Mind my getting mad I should
like to go back in ahead and open the party
so that I wasn't mine actually I'm kind
of black are all tied up now I run
a farm that we brush here
again. And I cannot.
Serve in cleaner already with this ad is
going on London go ahead late now and this
is are I
a twenty five single by the big buzzing
I got That's not by e-mail from Tomball
this morning he says everything is terrific
Oh well that is good news but tell me
have you heard from Tom. No How are things
Oh absolutely So I think we should have
a fantastic opening not tomorrow night
fantastic What about Allentown having
trouble getting
a carriage up at night although quite
the contrary she's been frightfully
conscientious go straight over the theatre
which knives Tom's the one who's been
romping about how I'm not sure what to do
cancel suffragette NO NO NO Tom's quite
well he's taken
a fancy to some girl of the show producer
the things he has to pay anyone I called
you call me after the opening when you
know that like the one is going to be
sitting and waiting and I
will oh boy I don't give it
a second thought but oh by the by How's
the mater our mamas firehose splendid do
give
a peck on the cheek for me I got to take
you tomorrow night to plow you know dig
you. I thought about me
that there
a man with some regiment it hasn't graded
it finally and you can get it exactly
going and after all when he's only
a week off I wonder what the groom is doing
morning let's call him in. Very funny
on the. One hand you can last night level
or on level I guess I don't I didn't pay
much attention
a lot of this was around too I have busy
little man he's PM time we were just
having
a few laughs just that's
all hunky. Command. While
it might be one of pleasant surprise you
know you I John Philip Tom I thought this
is going to presidency right now we have
a sensation of you oh well it isn't you
know that well right on the at once
organized them what time is bright which
are popular minutes and when you know how
to show them. It's been
a long time I know what
a duck to my neck of the up it does
give me a pie if I was OK OK I'll take
a little going out. On a huge
a bed and get myself like some of the
kids who get out of the van to miss my
opening night I didn't know my dad not
a moment and now. I get out of the.
Video game I'm like you know I mean my
mom I think about us I think about you
so get the spending out of the ball.
That's the ball I'm not going to hit
anybody or hit my daily ball. I
am
a new ball. Game and I think
that in many areas. A
lot. One of the right of
the can like my life for
a hold of all right where I'm coming from
by calling you know I'm Johnny I'm so
excited about him on the Monger I would
do it that there are five minutes ago who
didn't do it I think anyone out and I
together about three times as has been here
well along on just
a minute. That you're playing the song
she's supposed to be rehearsing but
there are now a lot of
choices of yeah oh that's
a good idea that you time. Right.
The the the.
The room.
All.
All all.
The you're the only.
Room. All
the.
The.
All.
Saw
a private. Forums are. All right
everybody that we are by I
started to work until late but about I
have two numbers we don't have to rehearse
the do
a final set no. Tell us pretty
good that's not bad and yet. We
get tomorrow night you know how could I
forget to try to make that we'd love to
have you know I met
afterwards that was giving
a party we'd go together
Tom I can count on
a telescope. That's right
forgot all about him well as I
wouldn't bother to have had such
a long time now I don't have to talk
back to back after I've been taught.
The time. What either of us. Three
o'clock or the company eleven thought of
me just. What time I want to go to numbers
we didn't do tonight I thought you
were satisfied with and still
a few rough spots. Say what haven't you
if you get to that are you talking about.
When a manic depressive
like you going to be
a marvelous particularly I'm
going to jump. In with you take.
The dog to. Dump it was the key you
have it I have not I gave it to you I
suppose I'd call it out the best and see
if you think nice thing all doors open to
. That's
a message for the day. I
wondered about him not
for me all that I know who I am
John can't make the open you can
on the chance had
a feeling this morning wasn't going to be
able to make it but he just didn't know
how to tell me I was in that terrible Now
isn't that terrible he's weak I just hate
weak people yes dear I know you
up one minute down the next what
a manic depressive life you'll
be. All right the words leave.
We're going with tomorrow night I don't
know what to take maybe think we should go
together anyway don't you after all with
the stars of the show is I think we should
Miss Bell and may I ask what you the
cleaners Clambake tomorrow night what I've
been laughing and what is the projects
can move get. Out that between
will be cosmic do and it
a smash we hope. And Alan Don't
forget but still the most important
thing. I know them tonight.
The police. Can be
after the first born God
Man Yes I'm sure I said it
might be
a saw was. Never the parting with you
when you put that right. Thinking
like one like me in the light and didn't
even know man I know at all but it would
to. Then I would likely use it to mean
yes if you mean I've got my clan thing
while you've been so I you know maybe I
don't but not the do you want. To let me I
don't know I got on I want to.
Get this one thing about you I kinda see
you and they say when I sang Love You know
when you know I've been
a liar all my. Get past it but you
can think you want me you you
must abandon saying that think I tell you
the truth I'm good I believe you when you
know baby Mary I know I'd
rather hang than have
a high. I know I say and make
you buy now when you know that
I would not want back all mine could do
but maybe when I sang i love you when
you're no a ban a liar. I have
a double dog why. I haven't gone gone T.
Then lie. You said you
would love the Mirage and
them would they run around then
into so they well you always.
Me Why baby you must be
looney to the low and. LOL to
a life he. Said I want.
A National Guard to do.
A half hour bungalow.
Bungalow you know you're
really naive to have
a baby bump up alone they don't they like
me my opinion of. You might want not to
know I happened upon a time when
a they and I was lyin I was
down in our bank. And.
The Y.
Was no and I would be out of the rip
a lot of pop even Begum I was
running from where I'm not on
a plank. Three baby leave us
not forget that I'm high heels.
Playing at Dartmouth why I now I've
been
a liar my mom I've got
car not them why. Thank
.
You.
But.
Thank you.
Thank.
YOU THANK YOU
YOU THANK.
The old I'm.
A campaign Night Man
irony of my blues band
ironic.
Thank
. You. Darling I just had
to come I just had. A
chat with the ex him yeah when they are
they've become very good friends oh yeah
that's it we're going to go to
a good mate. And I try not I don't
want to. But he did just the
open handed me you know I'm going on I
think it was oh I just walked out. I can
stand up in the US and I. And I think.
Oh what are we going to do about.
Congo on this day when I have.
No. That's not good. But
something might happen. While someday
my little my children see someone else.
The you.
The the.
All.
The the. The the they will all worry.
The room.
A very. Poor.
All the of.
The Earth.
All over the you.
The they. Are. I live or work.
To.
The or are
or
are. On the line.
Oh goodness oh. Well I met new
people found I guess a booking
a place to just get new ways. To get
about things of that. How could I.
Ever heard.
The the. Air.
In the wall. All.
We.
Must live the of the hour with
the earth.
Or are.
Or were.
Who is it me Jamie Tom.
I mean the boy coming on close up of the
night but it happened to. When I'm going
to go see you Tommy but I want the show
went well I I'm fine I Don't Feel Like
Going Home spread out of the party so I
thought I'd stop by and say hello when
you're just in town it was announcing go
to see the president on Monday I was at
the barber trying on the suits in the
palace and for the good you have
a look then you can tell me what to think
I think you're all by the way isn't this
and like to visit you yes you would by
about an hour go pick up and running and
store away like
a pig that or call come through from Chicago
now that bloomin bright and never call
she must be upset Well I couldn't say I
don't and it was about anything about me
she wanted to get to know but he cried yes
but the at least I hope she is but as is
waiting
a lot of her time being quiet well rested
and what do you think you might look like
a gentleman Jamie you look like
a banker or do I look like
a gentleman it's written all over it I got
it this afternoon compressing Monreal
last year when he got pneumonia the bottom
for him to be buried in but he recovered
well my only advice is if you meet the royal
family I wouldn't bow to luck remember
this is a wedding not
a coming out party I see what you mean I
know what you are you excited excited No
I'm just scared nervous and scared why it's
Meet me on call again I haven't clapped
eyes on her in the years I know it's
funny it wasn't for this royal wedding
probably I'd never have crossed her path
again I tell you what on Monday are called
going to get out of here I'll give you
moral support Now that's nice of you Tommy
unusually nice of you you're
a good man you know I don't know what Annie
is doing waiting for this knuckle and
she can do it you know the fellow like
you right here in town. That's love what
about you do I look like the settling
down time come on let me out.
The under the banning I'm dressed
for it I think it's only.
Like that but what if.
The poor.
Ad where. The everyone around
AUK. Everything that young and
a right of all I am after
a while there. Was.
No lie and I ruined my good
the New York bomb killed for
a day. Without my. Rolls by her door lock
Wal-Mart where all the and none will
lie at home at night in camp three.
And
a hot load now when the they.
Were all places that they made
bread was tired nor was
that your or was the or.
The A for. A board.
And you're. Born her.
Warmest floor or I had.
The board.
All red.
World.
It.
Out of the running so if you click then
test the notice is everyone you can stay on
for years if you see the daily Rob. This
be delayed we call it the library has been
awash with
a lot the lab results but that's what we
call it to get broken they want blocks of
seats. Right now so does anybody
think we're brilliant where
I can have I'm off to the office No I think
that really. If you sit down and think
what. I want to do a paper to
come out about when you call
a thing ask him to find
out what happened to
a boy who used to work in this department
store in Chicago his name is how Reiki I
bring it all down oh right you want to do
that and that don't seem right it should
be grave grave. This is
what you're ready and I'm
thinking here is I'm right oh.
Hey so I think buzzing right
a lot so I want to know that
this was that old but I was
a that bad huh no no no no was
a when oh well. Now look Tom
wants you to follow up on
a chap named Hal right already why deal
when all right now I want to see the single
Mr Reagan is not the theatrical
profession and the fantasy one is
a personal matter of the now and also
from Mr Reagan was employed over his
department store in Chicago of
a figure of a hassle to watch
a cover branch have the
whole message a lot but
a fast today that won't be necessary just
follow up on the right method and let us
know I just said this now oh yes.
Big. Oh says
Jane if you want to know he be they should
not take even other maybe the traffic is
not the fact he gets Jamie ever since I
told him I don't like to be kept waiting
he's been keeping the weight and you know
mother has no Spanish problems can you
does not love the phone seven not one
thousand I'd love to do that maybe well and
good for the Spanish but I'm English you
know what I think no deity I think is on
excited about seeing you think so how do
I look as elegant as can the Almighty
going to be going to last
forever could slow down
a little when you see the step of the big
one that the eyes of the royal couple
a factor when I stop in and what kind of
a goal it was slow it had gone its wrong
don't be so noble when you think of joy
act like the gentleman you love right I
will but it just says one word of criticism
I was wrong that it was his task with
your WE ARE stop your drive and.
Walk the rest of the way.
Trauma don't don't lose
your nerve get in there on.
For though Jamie would
a shout it Jamie just to Anthem
I'm so thank you. I'm back
I'm sorry I'm late the traffic was headed
today I told the guy but it was about to
become. So we go allow me Jamie don't.
I knew that whole there are some days when
you can do nothing wrong. You think that
again I'm sure I hope so for them as well
as I could never have another. Now you
can get mad we get about it. Good
evening. I have the information you requested
regarding the rate of what well it's
nothing terribly exciting Mr Raydon still
works at Ogilvy is it still in the
luggage department he used to live in
Chicago proper but not long ago he and his
wife moved didn't see why he
was resolute want to go. And
say Who is this chap in
a way he was engaged to
a girl I was just finding out about him for
her but I said it's frightful business
so please about I always
smile and hope I've got
a telescope not now don't
you think you should read
a lot of performance it would
seem kind of all right. You're
a real pal I'd stick up for you any time
thanks all Jeff that's frankly this if you
sit well if you were fielding power I
thought I should be around to pick you up
early tomorrow morning of tomorrow find
a royal wedding and I shall take you
someplace where you'll see all the pedantry
great actors and then write.
I left my hat. In Haiti. In
somebody's got to plant in
Haiti. I could tell you how I
got there I only know it was
sold out there he took my hat. Poli Sci.
Fi her arms around me I. I
remember they barely accept
the blame when she came
near me or are. The
higher ups around. And it was
a cameo. L.O.L.
I get in the moment with is that
people get up off your high you don't.
Pay. Their rent the girl
I'm all in favor. You can
find her your blood Dora just muck around
town you want someone who has gray.
I think about God just
reach up when I'm all.
And never I don't run down and hide there.
That's the goddamn hate. That's
gotten up really and had high hopes.
And plans this weekend to lay and live
his flat I think about patient do they.
Think Doug that is go get by.
I have my. Own Katie. And
Tom I've got platinum gave
me. The best car I've got I don't endorse
all rocks. In lands.
Group I remember being fairly
accept the blame when she's
a. Rock.
First. And I saw that again I.
Ignored. A. Girl I know in.
Your. Heart.
All right.
God All right
all right I'm glad
bomb Guangdong All
right.
All
right
.
All
right
all
.
The
Thanks Helen.
Ella got
a body to take home. Most
of the night. And I've
something to. Hope you won't think I'm one
of them where I should. Janey told your
friend that. I'd be told. I don't
quite know why I did it but I
decided to try and find out what
happened to you. Yes I did.
And. He's married man one on
one. Thing you want to.
Talk. Nothing and yet I've been wanting
myself to death over him on account of you
and he's been that I don't want to what do
you mean an economy meeting in love with
you being in love with me I'm
in love with you but I want to.
Want
a man. Because the next thing that happened
will be thinking about getting married
I've got it right not that easy
I don't want. Yes I do and
if you marry I'm afraid I can be married I
thought I've been the one way to me it's
always been work everything else side show.
It isn't because I don't want to it's
just that I I don't not like the
change. I know of you know what.
I think I do. What we
do have to take me how.
High are you back early
there's an early thought was.
This right.
I don't think. John wants to marry he
does that for me might be to you but it's
terribly serious to him very much in love
with me and said he found
a new phase and everything all on
account of me how do you feel. Very
constructive I never thought I'd live to
see the day you'd inspire anybody to do
anything but slug it out.
Go ahead but I'm. Sorry
you really are about this I want you have
to hear what he will do I don't know I
was rather hoping that make up my mind for
me why he usually does. Sure is funny
why you keep saying that when it isn't
funny at all it's very important I know I
only meant it's funny because. Man
wants me to marry her she does.
My. Sister is funny is that why well
I don't know it's just funny that's
all well what's so funny about
someone wanting to marry me I have
a few good points you know tell me I
really in love with me up to here.
Well I wonder what would
happen if we just do
a rollup and letterhead got married anyway
you'd stay here in England with John
rabbit I think you can't go
traipsing all over the world maybe
a hundred at home what kind of
a marriage without the. I suppose
not but what would you do
I'd Marianne and I know I mean how would
you then I never thought of that not
having you on my try and if she wants
to she loves to dance and shows
a lot of promise do you
really think so yeah. She was
a little awkward myself so were you when
you started I know it but I've yet to go
because you've always said that there's
a lot of exciting the doing it well that
just isn't there but isn't I'm getting the
short end of the stick want you want me to
settle back and get out of the way while
you were out with someone else and have all
the fun I think it's rotten time except
Iraq I've been mad at it we've
been so perfect We've had
a wonderful life together we've been
very successful haven't even considered
breaking it up and breaking up for what
to get married oh no time marriage is
a tough business for you know what I've
always I manage these obligations I want to
take care of maybe look more. To being
married to someone you're dancing with if
these are the marriage or the dance you've
gotten rid of all of them go completely
what will know how much this is
a terrible chance to take it isn't that we
must do what we say to try to get where
we are why should we give it up it doesn't
bully's doesn't return and I've got
a good we gotta stay that way maybe you're
right good God If I'm right when you do
see it don't you tell me sure I see it if
you want me just like it's always been
I'm sure we're doing the right thing thank
you so much for deciding to get it.
Right after the bat was. That right.
After the last. Lap. I had wrapped up
a. Half. And
half and I had.
One and love the day for the landing and
I will say. Look I would love to be in
that they play the role your God they don't
think I didn't think I thought I knew
all the men at fight or got time I think
they want to love if they don't play any
role with my dad I would say that's one
of them in the wedding. They're great big
nominees don't. Lie lay
a day.
Good morning Jeff they have a good body
I've come to think of the wedding and what
a wedding great we show the already that
is on everybody I said What's the matter
with you to the small you zero
six seven things about let's go.
Rah rah rah.
RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH RAH.
For.
Were. Wrong.
Wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong. On the. Enemy.
We must know that we want to get married I
say to the least one of them you want to
get me. We wait for anything after week
what you would think I mean if it went well
I know what the mission but the world
is busy and I have got this with. You
to give the big agenda to us all possible
to get this for life and to to the
American stuff to know what it was like
you're trying to make I know the minute
that it is this is
a pretty fucked up think we've got to get.
Out we have fun and I'm just going to
keep I know of course. You can always just
be nice and even that's what we're going
to find at least I'm going to miss
a lot of our. Good luck that you have
a. Lot
of. News in the. Mind of
what you think you do if
there's.
No. Way
a matter of days. When nobody. Moves
.
When world world will. Lose.
They didn't have that always problems
quality would have been all right.
Old. The
whole little.
Girl. In or.